https://architects.hpadesign.com/docs/privacy

Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer. Cookies typically contain information about the user (i.e. username, site display preferences, shopping cart contents, etc.) with regards to a specific website.
Information Collection and Use
HPA Design, Inc. is the sole owner of any and all information collected on HPAdesign.com and will NEVER, without your prior consent, disclose your personally identifiable information.
IP Address & Log Files
Your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other site usage data may be collected and used to gather broad demographic information. We use user IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user movement for aggregate use. Monitoring such user behavior enables HPA Design, Inc. to provide our users with an ever-improving site, service, and general offering. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.
Links
HPAdesign.com contains links to other websites. HPA Design, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of all sites they visit prior to sharing any personally identifiable and/or financial information.
Newsletter
HPA Design, Inc. publishes an electronic newsletter. This newsletter is issued through email on an opt-in subscriber base only. HPA Design, Inc. requires the provision of a valid email address by all subscribers. All other information is by request only and may be provided, in full or in part, at the subscriber's discretion. Any information provided becomes the sole property of HPA Design, Inc. and will NEVER be disclosed without your prior consent. Subscribers that no longer wish to receive the
Product & Service Orders
Our site uses an electronic order form to fulfill user requests for information, products, and services. HPA Design, Inc. may collect personal and financial information (i.e. name, address, credit card number, etc.) from users that order information, products, and/or services. Such information is collected through the use of SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encrypting technology and is used to process payment and shipping.
Security
HPA Design, Inc. takes every precaution to insure the security of user information, both online and offline. All sensitive information submitted through HPAdesign.com (i.e. credit card information) is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) firewall protection. Furthermore, HPA Design, Inc. does not store any personally identifiable or financial information online. HPA Design, Inc. also restricts access to such information by its employees. All employees of HPA Design, Inc. have been made awa
Supplementation of Information
We do not supplement our client information with any 3rd party information, nor do we ever provide information to any 3rd parties, without prior user consent.
Notification of Changes
HPA Design, Inc. reserves the right to make changes to its privacy policies without notice. Although changes to the policy may take place, under no circumstances will HPA Design, Inc. ever disclose any user's personally identifiable and/or financial information without his prior consent. Users should review the HPAdesign.com privacy policy periodically to insure that they remain informed.
Resources
FAQ's
Copyright
Licensing
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Glossary
New Client Form
